envelopes.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Envelopes.com

__TODAY'S DEALS

RECENTLY VIEWED 

#### All of Our Special Offers in One Place!

#### Your Recently Viewed Items

Want to pick up where you left off? Here are a few of your recently viewed items.

##### Privacy Policy

At Envelopes.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring the security of the information you submit to us. We want your use of the Envelopes.com web site, and the services we offer, to be productive and safe. Envelopes.com's Privacy Policy illustrates our commitment to your privacy and security. 

When you register at Envelopes.com, we request your name, e-mail address, phone number, postal address, ZIP Code, state, and country. We use this data to manage registrations, and, when you place an order, to contact you about your order and to print your return address on Envelopes.com envelopes. 

We may use your e-mail address, mailing address and/or phone number to contact you regarding new product offerings and other aspects of your use of the Envelopes.com web site. If, however, you do not wish to receive such communications, you have the ability to "opt-out" at any time. 

In order to take payment for your order, we collect credit card information. To maintain the highest level of security, your credit card information is encrypted using secure sockets layer (SSL) technology. SSL is secure server software that protects against any unauthorized access. Envelopes.com uses your credit card information for the sole purpose of accepting payment for your order. 

From time to time, we may ask you to answer surveys regarding current or future Envelopes.com products. Participation in these surveys is always optional. Survey responses are only used in the aggregate, and are never linked to an individual. While our survey data is primarily for use within Envelopes.com only, we may occasionally share the aggregate survey data with our development partners (e.g. web design, advertising and marketing agencies) in order to facilitate new product development. 

We may occasionally have a special relationship with another company, an entity that we think of as a marketing partner. By this we mean that a portion or version of our web site is integrated into our partner's web site or is integrated with our partner's content or branding. In such a circumstance, because we are jointly presenting our web site with our partner, and because the partner is referring customers to Envelopes.com, we may agree to share information with the partner as part of our formal contract with that partner, including confidentiality and use obligations and restrictions regarding how the partner may use the information. In these instances where Envelopes.com and a partner jointly promote Envelopes.com's Services, Envelopes.com may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address, and username as a result of the joint promotion of Envelopes.com. We only share this information for users coming to Envelopes.com from a partner web site. Again, at the point of registration, you have the option to "opt-out" of receiving e-mails or promotional materials. If you have linked to Envelopes.com through a marketing partner as described here, the web page you view will be co-branded with the marketing partner. If you would like information about the information use and practices of a marketing partner, Envelopes.com recommends that you view the policy of the marketing partner. 

##### Tracking Information

Like most every web site, the Envelopes.com web site records certain tracing information any time someone visits the site. For every web page that is viewed, our web server records an IP address, the operating system, browser version and the name of the page that was viewed. This information is not linked to any specific user and is used in the aggregate to maintain and improve the Envelopes.com web site. 

##### Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of information that is stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Envelopes.com uses cookies to track your order process without having to re-verify your password on each page of the site. Rather than storing this information on Envelopes.com's server, the cookie is stored in your computer and is activated only when you visit the Envelopes.com site. Your privacy and security are not compromised when you accept a cookie from the Envelopes.com web site. No one can access the information except Envelopes.com. 

##### Links to Other Sites

Our web site contains links to sites developed by other companies and organizations. Please be aware that these sites' privacy policies may differ from ours. 

##### "Opt Out" Policy

By default, we do not send Envelopes.com users any unsolicited e-mail. We only send notifications of product updates, etc., if a user has specifically requested this information. The choice of whether or not to receive these notifications can be changed at any time by sending an e-mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#f98a9c8b8f909a9cb99c978f9c9596899c8ad79a9694)

##### Updating Your Information

All of your personal information can be corrected or updated at any time by visiting the "My Account" section of the Envelopes.com site. 

##### Envelopes.com Website Security

The Envelopes.com web site uses secure sockets layer (SSL) to encrypt the transfer of sensitive information, such as your account password and billing information, from your web browser to our web server. 

The same SSL protocol also acts to authenticate the www.Envelopes.com site and prevent unauthorized "hackers" from masquerading as the Envelopes.com site. This is accomplished through a "digital certificate", which is an unforgeable electronic "identity card". 

If another website attempts to falsely identify itself as www.Envelopes.com, your web browser will display a warning indicating that there is a problem with the digital certificate for www.Envelopes.com. Do not log in to the Envelopes.com site if you see any such warning. 

##### How You Can Help Keep Your Information Secure

The most important step you can take to keep your information secure is to keep your password secure. Do not give your password to other people and avoid choosing "easily guessed" passwords (e.g. any single word in the dictionary, proper names of people and places easily associated with you, etc.). Change your password immediately if you suspect someone has been accessing your account without your permission (click on the "Profile" section of the Envelopes.com web site after logging in). If for any reason you suspect a security violation has occurred, please immediately send an e-mail to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#89faecfbffe0eaecc9ece7ffece5e6f9ecfaa7eae6e4) with a description of the situation. 

##### Your Consent

In addition to the circumstances described above, Envelopes.com may disclose or release information when we, in good faith, believe that doing so is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with the law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Envelopes.com, our users, or others. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Envelopes.com as described in this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our policy, we will post those changes here so you will always know what information we gather, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

If you have any questions regarding Envelopes.com's privacy policy and practices, please direct them to the Envelopes.com Support Team. 

##### Aggregate

When a site states that they collect information in the aggregate, they mean for summary purposes only. For example, sites that collect IP addresses "in the aggregate" do so to answer such questions as: "How many people from America Online visited our site last week?" 

##### IP Address

When you are connected to the Internet, your computer has a unique Internet ID called an IP address. Most people that connect through a dial-up service, such as America Online, get a different IP address each time they login. Others logging in from work or school might have a permanently assigned IP address, called a static IP address. It is difficult or impossible for a web site to collect personal information about you (i.e., your name, e-mail address, etc.) from your IP address alone, although a static IP Address can be used to identify a little bit more about you (i.e. your company name, or university name). 

##### SSL (Secure Sockets Layer)

SSL is a communication protocol that accomplishes two things: 

It allows your web browser to verify that a web site you're visiting is actually the site that you think it is (and not some site posing as another). 

It lets your web browser and a web server communicate with each other (i.e. pass web pages back and forth) in a completely secure fashion through the use of very strong encryption techniques. This encrypted communication makes it impossible for anyone else to see any information passed between your web browser and our web server.
